You're telling me
this actress person...
...is the only woman you ever wanted
who didn't want you back?
Oh, my God.
Is this what it's like to be you?
- You're crazy about her, huh?
- You have no idea.
When we're on-stage,
I get to kiss her and touch her.
She goes home with the director...
...and it's like somebody's
ripping out my heart.
It's so great to see you
feeling like this.
Dad called this morning.
Aunt Sylvia passed away.
Yes! Yes!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
We were all
pretty shaken up about it.
Am I missing something?
I always thought death was
supposed to be sad, in a way.
Well, Aunt Sylvia was...
...not a nice person.
She was a cruel, cranky old bitch.
And I'm sorry she died.
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
- You get the dollhouse.
- I get the dollhouse!
A house for dolls!
That is so cool.
When I was a kid, I had a barrel.
You had a barrel for a dollhouse?
No, just a barrel.
You know what? You can play
with my dollhouse.
- Really?
- Any time you want.
When I was younger, all I wanted
was to play with this dollhouse.
But no! It was to be looked at,
never played with.
My grandmother used to say
that exact same thing to me.
More of a bathtub-type situation.
She did give you one chance.
She told Monica she could play with
the dollhouse if she lost 20 pounds.
Yeah, well, look who's
losing weight now, Aunt Sylvia.
The One With the Doll House
Thanks for lunch.
You didn't have to walk me here.
That's okay. No problem.
You do realize we don't keep the
women's lingerie here in the office.
Yes, I realize that.
- Summer catalog.
- That's the stuff.
Rachel, I need the Versace invoice.
You don't work for me.
Joanna, this is my friend
Chandler Bing. Joanna.
Bing? That's a great name.
Thanks. It's Gaelic for,
"Thy turkey's done."
- I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you.
- You too.
So, what's wrong with him?
Nothing. He's just goofy like that.
I actually hardly notice it anymore.
No, no. I mean, is he married
or involved with anyone?
He's not married
or involved with anyone.
Well, Rachel...
Actually, you know what?
Forget it.
- I'll ask him for you, if you want.
- Would you?
Or is it too sad and desperate,
something that Sophie would do?
- I am here.
- I know that.
Look at it!
Wallpaper's a little faded.
That's okay.
Carpet's a little loose.
Hardwood floors?!
- It's so beautiful!
- I know!
So I'm here, ready to play!
I brought a bunch of stuff
for the house, so check it out.
What's this?
That's a dog.
Every house should have a dog.
Not one that can pee on the roof.
Maybe it's so big because the house
was built on radioactive waste.
And is this in case
the house sneezes?
No, that's the ghost for the attic.
- I don't want a ghost.
- Well, nobody wants a ghost.
But you've got one...
...because the house is sitting on
an ancient Indian burial ground.
Wait a minute. The house
was built on radioactive waste...
...and an ancient
Indian burial ground?
That would never happen.
Obviously you don't know much
about the U.S. Government.
- I need to talk to you.
- Sure. What's up?
Oh, sorry. I meant Chandler.
I know.
Well, if something comes up...
I'm glad you guys are past
that little awkward phase.
My boss. Joanna. When you left...
...she started asking questions
about you...
Liked what she saw?
Dug my action, did she?
Checking out the Chan Chan Man!
That was...
...surreal.
What do you think?
Are you interested at all?
Yeah. She seemed cool.
Attractive. I'll do it.
Thank you. This is so great.
She's gonna love me.
Dinosaur attack!
Quick, everybody into the house!
All right, Phoebe, you know what?
That's it. That's it. All right?
No dinosaurs, no ghosts,
no giant dogs, okay?
They're not the right size, they're
not Victorian and they don't go.
Fine.
Come, dinosaur. We're not welcome
in the house of no imagination.
While we're hovering around the subject,
I just have to say that dinosaurs...
...they don't go, "ruff!"
The little ones do.
- Hey, Kate.
- Morning.
I went to that restaurant
you were talking about...
Hey, lovely.
Come, talk to me for a minute.
And I ate the food. It was good.
I had the fish. Yeah, really good.
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
- Joey Tribbiani.
- I know.
I'm a big fan of yours.
What?
I used to schedule my classes
so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
...on Days of our Lives.
- Get out of here. Really?
- Absolutely.
But then they went and dropped you
down that elevator shaft.
They gave me the shaft, all right.
You're so funny.
What are you doing after rehearsal?
- Want to get a drink or something?
- Well...
Yeah. Sure.
A drink sounds great.
- Cool. I'll see you then.
- All right.
All right. It's time to act,
my talking props.
If you wanna make the
boys' bathroom realistic...
...you're gonna have to put some teeny,
tiny porno magazines behind the toilet.
Look everybody!
Look at my new dollhouse!
Look, look!
Hey, what's this?
It's a slide instead of stairs.
Look.
Very interesting, Phoebe.
What's this?
The licorice room.
You can eat all the furniture.
When guests come over, they can
stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
This is the coolest house ever!
Does anyone want to join me
in the Aroma Room?
- All right.
- I would.
Hey, guys? Guys!
Did you see my new china cabinet?
Watch. Watch.
And. And.
Hey, my father's house does that.
Okay. How did it go?
Tell me everything!
The movie was great...
...dinner was great, and there's nothing
like a cool, crisp New York evening.
Of course, I didn't enjoy any of that
because Joanna's such a big, dull dud!
Chandler is fantastic!
- What?
- We click! You know how people click?
He came by to pick me up, I opened
the door and it was just like, "click!"
Did he tell you?
He's got such a good heart.
Doesn't he have a good heart?
And he's so sweet. He said he'd
call, so put him straight through.
- Isn't this great?
- Don't spoil it.
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
What do you say?
It's you.
Just one sec.
I'm going to take this call.
When I continue, I hope
that there will appear on-stage...
...this magical thing
that in the theater we call...
...committing to the moment!
The guy's like a cartoon.
- What do you see in him, anyway?
- He happens to be brilliant.
Which is more than I can say
for that sweater you're dating.
I'm not interested in her sweater.
It's what's underneath her sweater
that counts.
And besides, since when do you care
who I'm going out with?
I don't care.
Why, do you want me to care?
Do you want me
to want you to care?
Do you?
What?
Okay. I'm afraid to say this,
but let's pick it up where we left off.
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
What do you say?
I've got no reason to stay.
Stop! Stop it!
You must stop!
You are bad actors!
This is a terrible play!
I'll see you in the morning.
I can't believe we go on
in a week.
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
So since we're getting off early,
do you want to go and paint mugs?
What?
At the place I told you about
last night?
Yeah, with the mug-painting.
I was so listening to that.
But you know what?
I need to work on my stuff tonight.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I guess.
What are we gonna do
about the scene?
I don't know.
Maybe if it had more heat.
Well, how do you mean?
Adrianne's looking
for a reason to stay, right?
Victor can't just kiss her.
He's gotta...
He's gotta really give her a reason.
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
Or maybe...
Maybe he could grab her,
and lift her up.
Then Adrianne could wrap her legs
around his waist.
She could do that.
And claw at his back.
Right. Then she could rip off his shirt
and kiss his chest and his stomach.
Then he could use his teeth
to undo her dress...
...and bite her!
And then right when the scene ends...
...he could take her
with this raw, animal...
Something like that?
Yeah. That's pretty much
what I had in mind.
It's a little early to be drinking.
Things finally happened with Kate.
- You're kidding?
- That's great.
It was so amazing.
After the lovemaking...
Oh, my!
...I just watched her sleep for hours.
Just breathing in...
...and breathing out.
And then I knew she was dreaming
because her eyes kept going like this:
I'm telling you,
Joanna's got it all wrong.
All I said was, "This was fun.
Let's do it again some time.
I'll give you a call."
I wonder why she thinks you're going
to call her?
That's what you say
at the end of a date.
You can't just say,
"Nice to meet you. Good night"?
To her face?
I'm so happy.
It's the end of the date.
I'm standing there...
...all she's waiting for is for me to say
I'll call her, and it just comes out.
I can't help it.
It's a compulsion.
When a guy says he'll call,
it doesn't mean he's going to call.
This never happened to you?
Well, they always called.
Bite me.
- Did he call?
- No, sorry.
Why? He said he'd call.
Why hasn't he called?
Maybe he's intimidated by really
smart, strong, successful women.
Sophie, will you please
climb out of my butt.
Why hasn't he called, Rachel?
Why?
Well, maybe he feels awkward
because you are my boss.
Awkward?
Why should he feel awkward?
The person that should feel awkward
is you. Did you tell him not to call me?
If you're uncomfortable with him
dating someone you work for...
...there are always ways to fix that.
Call her. Call her now!
Multiple so many paper cuts.
"Why hasn't he called, Rachel?
Why, why? I don't understand!
He said he'd call. Why?"
I'm telling you, she's flipped out!
She's gone crazy!
Well, give me the phone then.
This isn't funny. She thinks
it's my fault you haven't called.
- You have to call her.
- Look...
...you can't call somebody
after this long to say:
"In case you didn't notice,
I don't like you."
- Then you'll have to take her out again.
- No!
She's really dull,
and she gets this...
...gross mascara-goop thing
in the corner of her eye!
I don't care! You're gonna have
to take her out again and end it.
And end it in a way
that she knows it's actually ended.
I don't care how hard it is.
Don't tell her you'll call her again!
All right, fine! But it's just
a lunch date. No more than an hour.
From now on, I get my own dates.
I don't want you setting me up again!
That's fine!
- That's just a lot of big talk.
- I know.
I'm in the shower.
Fire! There's a fire! Fire!
I talked to Lauren.
I told her how things were with us.
Did you talk to Marshall?
About what?
About what happened with us.
No, and there's really no reason
why he should find out.
So let's not make a big deal
out of it, okay?
What are you talking about?
It was a big deal.
You can't tell me last night
didn't mean something to you.
I was there.
You're not that good an actress.
I was just caught up in the moment.
That's all it was.
Joey, I'm sorry you feel bad, but...
...haven't you slept with a woman where
it meant more to her than it did to you?
No.
- Hi, Kate.
- Hi, Lauren.
- Hi, pig!
- Sorry I scared you in there.
- It's okay.
By the way...
...I was just checking
the shower massager.
I tried to reach you at work.
There's been a fire.
What?
Oh, my God!
What happened?
We believe it originated here...
...in the Aroma Room.
Did everyone get out okay?
The giraffe's okay,
and so is the pirate.
- What is this?
- No, don't look!
You don't want to see
what's under there!
The foster puppets!
It's not a big deal. It's right
here, and it's all the time.
Well, thanks again for lunch.
- Yes. This was pleasant.
- It was, wasn't it?
- The food there was great.
- Wasn't it?
So take care.
You too.
This was great. I'll give you a call.
We should do it again!
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
- Rachel, any messages?
- Sophie's desk.
- Are you gonna call her?
- No.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm weak
and pathetic and sorry.
You are gonna tell her.
You'll tell her now.
I'm not gonna call you.
What?
I'm sorry that I said I was going to
when I'm not.
It's just that I was trying to be nice,
and you don't deserve that.
- I see. I think.
- Look, this has nothing to do with you.
And this isn't Rachel's fault.
It's me.
I have serious problems
when it comes to women.
I have issues with commitment,
intimacy...
...mascara goop.
I'm really sorry. It's just that
this isn't going to work out.
Well, this isn't how
I was hoping this would end...
...but I guess I have to appreciate
your honesty.
Yeah. Okay.
So...
This is great. I'll give you a call.
We should do it again!
So anyway, Beth,
what I'm saying is...
...I should have considered your
feelings before I went home with you.
I've recently learned what it's like
to be on your side of it...
...and I'm sorry.
So do you think
you can forgive me?
Great. Thanks.
Okay. Bye.
Hello, Jennifer?
Hi, Mrs. Laurio.
Is Jennifer there?
She's not home, huh?
Well, actually,
I need to talk to you too.